const STORE = [
    {
        //Question 1
        question: 'anomaly',

        answerOptions: [
        'a difference or contrast between similar things or people',
        'a level of quality or attainment',
        'relating to or characteristic of animals',
        'something that deviates from what is standard, normal, or expected'
        ],

        correctAnswer:
        'something that deviates from what is standard, normal, or expected',
   
        exampleSentence:
        'Those years were just an anomaly, historically speaking, the Commander said.',

        exampleSource: 
        'The Handmaid’s Tale'
    },
    {
        //Question 2
        question: 'cacophony',

        answerOptions: [
        'an event causing great and often sudden damage or suffering; a disaster',
        'a harsh discordant mixture of sounds',
        'having the same or similar sounds',
        'the quality of forming a pleasing and consistent whole'
        ],

        correctAnswer:
        'a harsh discordant mixture of sounds',
   
        exampleSentence:
        'Tyrion put his spurs to his horse and added one more voice to the cacophony, and the van surged forward.',

        exampleSource: 
        'A Game of Thrones'
    },
    {
        //Question 3
        question: 'dissonance',

        answerOptions: [
        'a close parallel or repetition of an idea, feeling, style, or event',
        'a loud and confused noise, especially that of people shouting vehemently',
        'a tension or clash resulting from the combination of two disharmonious or unsuitable elements',
        'the condition of being far off; remoteness'
        ],

        correctAnswer:
        'a tension or clash resulting from the combination of two disharmonious or unsuitable elements',
   
        exampleSentence:
        'It’s doubtful that watching Nancy Drew get busy will be a deal-breaker for most people; a slap of cognitive dissonance for some, definitely.',

        exampleSource: 
        'Salon, October 8, 2019'
    },
    {
        //Question 4
        question: 'aberration',

        answerOptions: [
        'a departure from what is normal, usual, or expected, typically one that is unwelcome',
        'cruel and bitter criticism',
        'offense or annoyance',
        'the action or fact of making a specified thing smaller or less in amount, degree, or size'
        ],

        correctAnswer:
        'a departure from what is normal, usual, or expected, typically one that is unwelcome',
   
        exampleSentence:
        'Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg said Thursday that the current political climate will be seen as “an aberration” in U.S. history.',

        exampleSource: 
        'Washington Times, October 3, 2019'
    },
    {
        //Question 5
        question: 'vitriol',

        answerOptions: [
        'a departure from what is normal, usual, or expected, typically one that is unwelcome',
        'a tension or clash resulting from the combination of two disharmonious or unsuitable elements',
        'cruel and bitter criticism',
        'the action or fact of making a specified thing smaller or less in amount, degree, or size'
        ],

        correctAnswer:
        'cruel and bitter criticism',
   
        exampleSentence:
        'That isn’t an unfair or unlikely view of the world, but it’s a simplified one that ignores more significant issues, like virtual harassment and online vitriol.',

        exampleSource: 
        'The Verge, October 10, 2019'
    },
    {
        //Question 6
        question: 'umbrage',

        answerOptions: [
        'a close parallel or repetition of an idea, feeling, style, or event',
        'a departure from what is normal, usual, or expected',
        'offense or annoyance',
        'the presentation of something as being smaller, worse, or less important than it actually is'
        ],

        correctAnswer:
        'offense or annoyance',
   
        exampleSentence:
        'It seems that the chef she spoke with took umbrage not just with the request for a special, non-menu item, but also that they not be charged full price for the meal.',

        exampleSource: 
        'Fox News, September 21, 2019'
    },
    {
        //Question 7
        question: 'tyro',

        answerOptions: [
        'a beginner or novice',
        'a person exercising power or control in a cruel, unreasonable, or arbitrary way',
        'a person who dislikes humankind and avoids human society',
        'a person who seeks to promote the welfare of others'
        ],

        correctAnswer:
        'a beginner or novice',
   
        exampleSentence:
        'The first when I was a young tyro cutting my peripatetic teeth; the latter just 18 months ago, when a confirmed flounderer in the murky depths of middle age.',

        exampleSource: 
        'The Guardian, June 21, 2019'
    },
    {
        //Question 8
        question: 'polemic',

        answerOptions: [
        'a departure from what is normal, usual, or expected, typically one that is unwelcome',
        'a strong verbal or written attack on someone or something',
        'a tension or clash resulting from the combination of two disharmonious or unsuitable elements',
        'the action or fact of making a specified thing smaller or less in amount, degree, or size'
        ],

        correctAnswer:
        'a strong verbal or written attack on someone or something',
   
        exampleSentence:
        'Bloom’s cultural polemics were sharp-tongued and colourful, but his smile was warm and boyish.',

        exampleSource: 
        'The Guardian, October 14, 2019'
    },
    {
        //Question 9
        question: 'precipitate',

        answerOptions: [
        'bring about abruptly',
        'dispute the truth, validity, or honesty of (a statement or motive); call into question',
        'make (something) ready for use or consideration',
        'speak or act in an evasive way'
        ],

        correctAnswer:
        'bring about abruptly',
   
        exampleSentence:
        'Davis describes the aftermath of his Paris tour in 1949 and 1950—the anguish of his return to the relentless racism of the United States—as precipitating his heroin addiction.',

        exampleSource: 
        'The New Yorker, August 28, 2019'
    },
    {
        //Question 10
        question: 'vacillate',

        answerOptions: [
        'alternate or waver between different opinions or actions; be indecisive',
        'cause or give rise to (a feeling, situation, or condition)',
        'cause (someone) to feel drained of energy or vitality; weaken',
        'speak or act in an evasive way'
        ],

        correctAnswer:
        'alternate or waver between different opinions or actions; be indecisive',
   
        exampleSentence:
        'The main opposition Labour Party is itself deeply split over Brexit, and appears to be vacillating about whether to launch a motion of no-confidence to try and bring Johnson down.',

        exampleSource: 
        'Reuters, September 24, 2019'
    }
]